We'll start off the India implementation by adding a couple of new files to go over to the main folder,
right click and add a new head of file.
And call it at Investment H.
Now, let's add a new source file.
And call it app and voice, Dorsey.
Now go over to see make lists.
Into the sources, let's add up in voice gutsy.
And now let's get organized you.
Because now we'll start off in the EPP and vice head of file.
And he will create a few functional prototypes.
So let's first comment you.
Safe station mode.
WI fi credentials.
To envious.
And the return is OK.
If successful.
And it's Espero type.
App and voice save state creds.
And it's void.
Now, let's make another.
Which loads the previously saved.
Credentials.
From Vice.
And the return.
Is true, if previously saved credentials were found.
And the return is bull.
And its app and voice load.
Stay creds.
And it's void.
Now, let's make another.
Which clears station mode credentials.
From NCVHS.
And the return.
Is ESP OK, if successful?
So the return is Espirito.
And we'll name it app and voice.
Clear state creds.
And it's void.
All right, so that's our three prototypes now, let's copy them so we can define them in the C file.
And let's paste them here.
Now we need to include.
Vestibule, that edge.
We also need to include here.
Studio.
And let's also include String Derrick.
And now include.
VSP looked Dunwich.
We also need to include envious flesh.
Duddridge.
And we also need our.
Our app and vestige.
And also include.
Why fi app Duddridge?
And next, let's add a tag.
For logging to the monitor.
And it's a static const care tag.
And let's call it envious.
OK, now we need our NCVHS name space used for station mode credentials.
And it's Konst Chair, app and voice star creds namespace.
And let's call it state creds.
OK, so next, let's define the save state creds function, and we'll need an envious handle.
And call it handle.
And then ESPN aired tape.
Esper.
And now S.P. lug.
That this function.
Is saving station mode credentials.
To flesh.
Now we need a Wi-Fi config type.
Pointer and call it wi fi SDH config.
Now, let's use our wi fi app.
Get wi fi config function.
Right, and if you recall that this function will return the Wi-Fi configuration like some.
And you will need to confirm the validity of this point to before continuing to use it to save credentials
to flesh.
So he will say if we fight state config.
And in here, we'll begin our investor operations and say Esper.
Equals and vice open.
And they'll pass the name space.
And then open in voice read write mode.
Out handle is a reference to the handle.
And then say, if ESB error.
Is not equal to ESP, OK?
Then we'll print.
That R function.
There.
Opening envious handle.
And let's use the spare to name function to get the error.
All right, so say ESP error to name.
In Pass, Esper.
And then we'll return to ESPÉRER.
OK, so now, let's say, set aside.
And it's Esper equals and vice set blub.
And passed the handle.
And then the key is.
And the value is why fi SDR config, SDR.
Aside, and the length is our max assisted length.
And now we'll check the air status and say if.
ESP error is not equal to ESP, OK?
Then let's print the error.
The same as before, so we can copy this.
And then say they're setting aside to invest.
All right.
And next, we can set the password in the same manner.
So let's copy this one.
And pace below.
And let's change this to password.
And change the key to password.
And the value is the password.
All right, in the print message is password.
So next.
We can commit credentials.
Two knives.
So let's do ESP air equals envious commit.
Pass the handle.
And now let's do the checking, let's say, if spare is not equal to ESP, OK?
Then let's print the message and return the error.
It will change this to committing credentials to.
Right.
And next, let's call envy as close in past the handle.
Now, S.P. Lug.
That the function.
Wrote Why five state config?
Station, as you said.
And we'll print it and password.
Animal print that.
And then we'll pass wi fi esta config.
Staked aside and why fi SCA config stay.
Password.
All right.
And now let's print that.
The function.
Returned ESP, OK.
Now, actually, let's return ESB, OK?
OK, so we return, OK, if all went well.
All right, so next, let's do the load state credits function here.
All right, so now I'll get this interview.
And first, let's create an invoice handle here.
And its handle.
And we needed spare time, ESP Air.
And now let's ISP lug.
That the function here.
Is loading Wi-Fi credentials?
From flesh.
And I will say if.
Envious is open in past the space.
And it's envious, read only.
Pass a reference to the handle.
And if that returns, ESP, OK.
Then we'll open up the curly braces.
And then we'll say else.
Put our return false you.
Now, let's go back up to the successful case, and we need a Wi-Fi config type pointer.
WI fi SJ config, and let's use a wi fi app, get wi fi config function.
And now we need to check the point to and say, if we stay config, there's no.
Then we'll want to allocate memory for it.
So say we fight stay config.
Equals.
Why fi config type cast pointer and now, Malak?
For the size of.
Why fi config type?
Next, we need to set the five star config.
Two zero.
For the size of Wi-Fi config type.
OK, so next, we need to allocate a buffer.
And let's use size T.
Why fi config size?
Equals size of the white flight config type.
And now we need a U.S. aid point to call it white flight config buffer.
Equals UNT eight typecast.
Malak.
Signs of.
UNT a type.
Multiplied by the wi fi config size.
OK.
And that ensures our buffer is large enough.
So now Mims said the Wi-Fi config buffer.
Two zero.
For the size of.
Wife iwconfig says.
And that ensures that buffer is clear.
Right, so next, let's load the suicide.
And we'll see if I can fix size.
Equals the size of wi fi star config.
As to that essence, I'd.
OK, next, use Espérer equals envious, get love.
Now past the handle.
Key is the suicide.
And the value as a wife, I can see buffer.
And the length is a reference to a wife iwconfig size.
OK.
And then say, if Esper is not equal to ESP, OK?
Then we need to free the memory, so say free wi fi config buffer.
And then let's print.
That dysfunction.
Now, let's give the air.
And say no station, as the side found in Vice.
And then use the air to name.
And pass the SPRO.
And now return false.
All right, so now we need to copy the suicide retrieved from flesh to our application by config.
So here let's use MEMC copy.
To our Wi-Fi star config.
Stay put aside from the wife iwconfig buffer.
For the Wi-Fi config size.
OK, great.
So next, we need to load the password.
So let's just use the same routine here so we can copy this one above.
And now let's use it below.
Now, let's change this comment here to load password.
And change this to password as well.
And just so you're aware this is our accessing the information from this structure.
Right here.
OK.
So next, let's change the key to password.
And for the printed text, let's change that.
And let's just change it to.
Change it to retrieving password.
All right.
So now we want to copy.
To the password.
OK, so here we're using the password key to load the password into our Wi-Fi config buffer.
And if successful, we copy it to state that password config.
So next, let's free the memory, so we'll say free wi fi config buffer.
And then let's call in as close in past the handle.
And now we'll print that.
The dysfunction.
Found a suicide email printed here and password.
And we'll printed you.
And now give it the wife stay config.
Stay DUT assisted in the fight.
Stay config.
A state that password.
And now it's confirmed that the credentials loaded by returning.
Why fight state config?
Staked aside in the first position, and if it's not equal to a no character.
Then we'll know that it returned true.
OK, so this return statement confirms that we actually have an SSD loaded.
All right, so let's continue.
To the clear state creds function.
And let's start here by creating an envious handle.
We also need an SPRO type.
He espérer.
Now, let's log.
That the clear state creds function.
Is clearing Wi-Fi station mode credentials from flesh?
And first of all, ESB Air.
Equals in vice open.
Pass the name space and it's envious, read write mode.
And it's a reference to our handle.
Now we'll see if the is not equal to ESP, OK?
And then we'll print that.
That a function.
Resulted in error and will print the error.
And we'll say opening envious handle.
And then use ESP Air to name.
Past the ESB air.
Pass the ESPOIR here.
Now we return the error.
OK.
So next, we'll erase credentials.
And then do ESB error equals in race all?
And pass the handle.
And say, if aespa error is not equal to ESP, OK?
Then let's print.
And say.
Error erasing station mode credentials.
And then I'll fix the spelling here.
Now, let's return the air.
OK.
And next, we can commit clearing credentials from envious.
And then do ESB Air.
Equals envious commit.
In pass the handle.
And say, if Esper.
It's not equal to ESP, OK?
Then we'll print.
This time will say.
Air envious commit.
OK.
So now we can envy as close.
The handle.
And then we can print.
There are clear state creds function.
Returned ESP, OK.
And now we can return ESP, OK?
All right.
That looks good.
OK, so but I have one mistake up here.
This password length, this should actually be Max password length.
And one more thing, the spelling up here should be const.
All right, so now let's build a project to make sure there's no errors.
OK, so that looks good.
So in the next lesson, we'll put these functions to use.